Imagine if I could transport you to a
world where you do the exact same amount
of
work that you're doing now,
but you get more clients as a byproduct.
I've been working with over 1,600 coaches
over the last 14 months, and although it
doesn't sound very sexy,
the way I help people achieve that goal
is by roasting
them, whether it's social media,
their marketing medium, their sales page,
or their
offer.
And four brave strangers have given me
permission to roast them
constructively.
If you would like to put your hat in the
ring to have me do one of
these critiques to your business,
fitness or not, there is a link in the
description, and you can apply now.
I thought today we would start with
fitness businesses.
And a quick promotion for any of you
that haven't tried Nutonic,
if you live in the
United Kingdom or the United States,
I'll put a link in the description and a
cheeky discount that I shouldn't have
shared with you because that
was supposed to
be for my online training clients.
But anyway.
The first person, Emmett Mullen.
I don't mind the profile
picture.
I feel like we maybe could've zoomed in a
little bit more.
There's a little bit too much of the
background.
We don't really need this nipple height
part here, so we can maybe crop in a
little bit on that so we can see your
face. This username is horrendous.
Emmett underscore... Let me just. "Hey,
bro, what's so good to catch you up.
You said you're a trainer.
What's your Instagram handle?" Yeah, sure.
It's Emmett, E-M-M-E-T-T,
in case you never know how to spell
Emmett, underscore, yeah, EJX2,
letter two, coaching,
underscore. What? Now, first things first,
it's worth
noting I have not pre-looked at any of
these people's content, I promise
you. With a name like Emmett Mullen,
you best believe you have got
emmettmullen.com with a dash in, 20 cents,
emmettmullen.biz, $11, 11mullen.online,
$1.29.
This does not happen for someone with a
name
like James Smith. James Smith sucks.
1,100. Cheers. Thanks for that.
So the name is aids,
to be changed immediately, please. EJX2.
I have to get my uncle out, Uncle ChatGPT.
It refers to EJX2 Coaching,
a coaching specialist service
founded by Emmett Mullen. So you made
that up.
There's a lot going on in the bio,
training tips, online
and one-to-one triathlon
coach, blood lactate testing,
that's a bit different, BSc/MSc in sports
performance, get coached by me.
So annoyingly, the very part that
is important
about this, about clicking the link,
they can't see. It needs to be populated.
If we took out the blood lactate testing,
and I do hope that these are in
order of the most important things first.
Training tips.
Let's just get rid of that,
suddenly your link is visible.
Get coached by me, click the link. Okay.
We got some good views on these bad boys,
230, 400K.
5.3 miles per hour up a 13.5% gradient,
keeping your heart rate-
I can't say I'm blown away by either of
these, but they did well.
And apparently triathletes
are a bit mental.
They spend more money on getting better
than any other athlete, I believe.
See,
some people try using this as a visual
hook, where they're like, "Look at me,
I'm on my phone. This
is important." I would much rather you
would look down the
camera. So you say in your caption here,
"Two and three mins, this is insane."
So you could've just looked at the camera
and gone, "What I'm about to show you is
insane." Boom, gone to the clip.
That should be full screen.
Because here you're insinuating
that you're as important as the clip,
but really if
this is the thing you're going to talk
about, just expand it and have it as an
overlay.
There is no need for you to be there with
your bikes in the background.
Bored.
Maybe it's because I don't do triathlons.
We could talk about content all day,
but let's go into here, Linktree.
Six-week sustainable running plan PDF.
Mate, this is not good.
This could be the best plan in the world,
but this looks like someone in year seven
has put it together.
If this is important to you, and this
is something that potentially you have out
there to show people that you
are a good triathlon coach, please never
ever sign off as EJX2 Coaching because
you're not
EJX2 Coaching. You're Emmett.
Just be Emmett.
All your clients are like, "Yeah,
Emmett is a fucking legend,
man." No one is like,
"Ugh, who's my coach?
EJX2 Coaching?" They're just not doing
that.
So bro, you could send this to Fiverr
or Upwork and get a graphic designer
to redesign this for 40 pound,
and this could be something
impressive. But even then,
it shouldn't be here.
I shouldn't be able to get this
if it's that good.
Instead,
you could've had ManyChat set up in your
social media.
"Hey, comment the word six,
and I will send you over a plan."
And then DM goes,
"Hey, it's Emmett.
Why don't you give me your best email
address, and I'll email it
across straight away?
Because this plan's really good,
do you mind if I send you a
few more emails over the next few weeks?"
And then they opt in for more marketing.
That, done completely wrong. Endure:
The Athlete Story
podcast. Let's check this out. Okay.
Endure: The Athlete Story.
Let's have a little look on the old tube.
Four videos.
Oh, haven't posted in three years.
On average, your videos are four
and a half years old.
Okay. Get coached by me.
Coaching application.
I think we're about to fall out, mate.
I've never even met you.
What the fuck, mate? I mean, who
are you learning
this from? Okay.
This isn't a Soho House membership.
I shouldn't have to apply.
Imagine there's a local Italian restaurant
in your
neighborhood. You call up, you're like,
"Oh, I'd like to book a table." "You'll
need to apply." Apply for a table tonight,
7:00 PM at Pazia.
Bro, let me tell you this,
I could have just done the worst triathlon
time
in all of Australia,
and I could've Googled online who the best
coach is, and
someone could've said, "Mate,
check out EJX2." I come on here,
and I'm ready to
buy. I go here, I click on that, I'm gone.
I have and will never fill out one of
these.
Do you want to know a short story I've
never told anyone before?
Gary V DM'd me,
asked me about speaking at an event in
Sydney, sent me a link,
came through to a type form.
I never did it. I never will.
I want to know a few things, what it is,
how much it costs, what I get,
and why I should believe you.
[sighs] Your bounce rate, well,
first of all, no
offense,
I don't think you're sending too much
traffic to here, if I'm completely
honest.
But your bounce rate must be phenomenal.
The amount of you using a type form will
have this confirmation bias.
Maybe you get a lead every week
and you're like, "Oh, cool." But
if you had the
analytics and the data,
which I'm not sure you would get,
of how many people visit
this and just fuck off,
you would be depressed by it.
This Linktree is redundant. You said,
"Get coached by me.
Click the link." Well,
I can't get coached by you by clicking the
link.
You should say, "Apply here"
or "Use the shitty type form.
Click below." You need to rebrand.
I know you've been doing this for seven
years,
but your brand should just be Emmett
Mullen.
I remember some of the rugby teammates
that I played with
growing up used a running coach called
Margo Wells I still
remember her name.
I don't remember the company.
I remember people.
Whatever you think EJX2 is, it's not.
It's you that people buy into.
If you look at your bank account at all
the
transactions,
of all the things people have ever bought
from you, trust me, they
are buying into you, your expertise.
So we can modify testing as well to suit
your need.
No hook.
If you're neglecting this crucial part of
race day performance, then you could be
throwing away minutes. You see,
so often people arrive at their race
without
putting any thought into their transition.
See, this could be, "Are you someone
that arrives to your race without putting
any
thought into your transition?" No hook.
Here's an unpopular opinion.
Not bad.
A chicken tender isn't always a bad thing.
Of course-
I would love to see some hooks in your
content that work backwards from people's
problems. I'm sorry, this can sound harsh.
I'm giving this a two
and a half out of 10. Good news is,
easy fixes right here.
Easy bloody fixes. One gripe.
So your YouTube
videos were like three to seven years old.
So you've been active as EJX2.
This brand isn't new.
Let's conservatively say six years.
Six times 365 is 2,190 days.
You've done like
one Instagram post a week.
400 posts in seven years. Come on, bro.
It's not active enough.
Mine's got like 4,500 posts.
I've been busy. Okay. Sorry, Emmett.
Give me your money, I can help.
Don't forget, if you want to apply,
there's a link in the description.
And buy NutriNIC, you bastards. Okay,
this one, Amelia.
I've met you several times, Amelia,
at IFS. How are you?
Does that mean you're safe from a roast?
Well, let's find out. Okay.
Do you know what I love about this?
Branding. Just name.
I take it it's Amelia Lang.
If that's not spelt Lang, I know.
Peach Parfait,
online female fat loss coach. Cool.
Establishing exactly who you are,
what you're doing.
Helped over 300 women drop fat
and love what they see in the mirror.
Appeal to authority, making it very clear.
If I just got 10 seconds to look at your
screen, I know very much what's happening.
"With zero restrictions,"
that probably could be, I don't know,
it's a bit
redundant.
"DM me 'ready' for more info." Okay.
I've DM'd you, and nothing's happened.
Could've been a very simple chatbot
automation.
You could've even just said, "Hey,
thank you so much for sending me that.
I'm away from my phone at the moment.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can."
Cool.
It's been aired.
I could've looked through your socials
and been like, "I'm so
ready," and then I've just got nothing
from it.
That's a real simple low-level automation
to put in there.
I'm not a big fan of this.
What you're trying to do
is just do something.
You're trying to get the caption to do the
work.
Some people are doing this to game the
algorithm because, say this is a second
video,
to read that might take someone 35
seconds, so you'd get a average view
duration of maybe three,
four times because the amount of time
someone's had to sit
through the video to read the caption.
I don't like it.
It doesn't help me build a relationship
with you as a coach, as I'm going to trust
you. I want to listen to you talk.
I want to get to know you.
I want to know about the idiosyncrasies,
which are the things that make you
unique to you. Now,
even just here from a snapshot,
we've got your outlier post
here. On average,
let's say we're hitting like 5,000 to
10,000 views per
reel. Here you have an outlier.
So this one here.
No matter what-
"3 big signs your calories
are too low." We should've hit this again.
Even here.
Confused at being told to drop your
calories to 1,200-
There is a content bucket here
that you've stumbled across.
I don't know if you know,
but talking about calories being too low
is doing well.
So I would like to see a video from you
that uses this, "3
big signs your calories are too low,"
but do it to camera.
"I'm Amelia, and these
are three signs that your calories
are too low." Scene
change. I don't know.
You could use a prop.
Talk about,
what do we use in the realm of women?
Feeling the cold.
You could put loads of layers on.
"You ever feel like you're cold all the
time?
This is a sign that your calories
are too low." Then you could go somewhere
and be
like, "Oh," stomach rumbles. Anyway,
it's good.
So it looks like the audience could be
from disordered eating, which
is pretty much
the fitness industry.
Let's go to your Linktree.
"Inquire to find out more information
about my coaching." Okay, let me tell you
this.
Say you want to go buy a new outfit from
Lululemon.
You go to the website,
there's the pricing, you peruse,
you can buy.
You get excited.
People like being excited.
Today, I came back from the beach,
had a wonderful swim at the sea,
and I decided
I want a copper shower outside my house.
I went online.
I found a company
that do nice copper showers,
and it wasn't cheap.
But I went to buy now,
and it turns out
that although they're based in Sydney,
they're not going to deliver to my house.
I was red hot.
I would've paid anything because
when I came back from the sea, it
was a perfect
picturesque moment.
I had to use a hose to wash myself down,
and I thought,
"James, you know what?
You're doing too well in life,
and your cars are far too
nice to be..." Imagine that.
There you are.
You know the guy with the nice Porsche?
Yeah, has to hose himself down. I
was like,
I've imagined a world where I've got a
nice copper shower. Two days' time,
it's going to be cloudy, and if
that guy calls
me back and goes, "James,
still interested in that copper...?" No,
I'm not.
I'm not interested in that copper shower.
I was hot then, I'm not anymore.
Begone, brother. Someone could be here.
They've just been dumped by their
boyfriend. They're ready to make change.
They're ready to commit.
They've been thinking about this for ages,
and this is
just underwhelming.
And do you know what I don't like here?
"If you found the perfect program to
achieving your goals, would there be any
reason why you couldn't start straight
away?" You are looking for something in
the
sales strategy to get them on a call
and pressure them into it.
I'm not saying this is the tactic
that you use, but this is why it's here.
And this doesn't need to be here.
In any of these type forms, "What is your
occupation?
Does it keep you active?" You're not
asking that.
You're trying to figure out their budget,
because if they say that they're a
managing director or they're a business
owner or they've got sniffer
self-employed.
I hate this. It is disingenuous. Look,
what it is, what
people say about it, what they get,
how much it costs. Because guess what?
If you can't afford it, that's fine.
And even if you don't buy now,
at least you know.
So you can go away,
you can explore the market.
Someone else might go, "Yeah,
join my mentorship. It's $10,000."
And you go, "What?
I could do an intense 10-week course with
James, being on the phone with him every
week for that.
I'm joining his." I'll show you.
It should be purple.
I find myself some days over here.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Over the next two years,
I'm thinking this is gonna be my next car.
I love it.
I look at it. I can't afford it yet.
But when I'm ready, I'll go buy it.
Do you know why?
Because I know how much it is.
If Lamborghini said, "Hey, James,
why don't you come in
and we'll talk about the
pricing?" I'd go, "How much
is it?" "Come in and we'll talk pricing
when you get
there." Imagine a restaurant. "Hey,
come in for tacos." "How much
is it?" "Let's
talk pricing once you've had your
entrees." I hate this.
Just get rid of this.
You've got personality.
You've got charisma.
Would it be too difficult for you to just
sit there, "Hi, I'm Amelia," tell people
about you. "My online coaching, this
is my style, this is how I like to do it.
Yes, I know it costs this much,
but this is what you get." Because then
people can
go away. They can think about it.
They can let their emotions simmer,
and they can
come back and be ready.
Because as it stands,
I've got to fill out your damn stupid
form.
Then I've got to jump on a call with you,
and at that point, it embarrasses
me if I don't buy it,
because I feel like I'm wasting your time.
And I guarantee any of you using these
type forms or doing sales calls, you may
get people over the line.
But I know your retention is dog shit,
because half of
the people that came just felt bad on the
call and signed up.
There should be full transparency with
your pricing.
The worst part is, not even,
let's park your clients to the side.
You're leaving money on the table doing
this.
A well-curated landing page could've been
so good. Free women's calorie calculator.
Should be getting someone's email address
for this. There you go.
Discover your TDEE. Cool.
That's all right. My YouTube vlogs.
Don't call it a vlog.
No one cares about vlogs, I'm afraid.
"How I lost fat, toned up,
and transformed my body.
I stopped fasting." Probably didn't need
to put "I stopped fasting" in that.
Definitely need a little bit of work on
your thumbnails.
The problem on this is you
are repeating the title in the thumbnail.
There is a perfect opportunity for you to
have something else that creates
intrigue. Let's go to your last video.
12 days ago. Okay.
Are you a A petite woman.
Maybe you're under
5'5"
and you're struggling with
that skinny fat look
Confident on camera.
You probably got a lot of traits
that women would love to
have. They're going to look at you and go,
"What a babe.
I wish I could wear a pair of high-waisted
leggings so that I could..." Do you know
what most women would dream about?
Standing in front of camera,
putting their hands on their hips
and looking like
that. This,
you need to have a sales video just
telling people how it is, and
also to put people's mind at ease.
Imagine you in front of camera.
"Hi, it's Emilia. This is my program.
Just before we get into the details,
I'd like to let you know, as a woman, it's
very difficult to find a coach
that not only gets you the results,
that you can
sustain. So for this reason,
if you're watching this video,
I'll give you a
three-month money-back guarantee.
If at any point in the next three months
you don't think I'm the perfect coach for
you, you let me know." Hearing
that from you,
I think would five times your
sales.
Petite woman, maybe
your dream body.
Well, me too, until
I did these three things.
[upbeat music]
I think you should carry on with the
YouTube.
And the thing here, a lot of people
are guilty of this on social media at the
moment. They're like,
"Here's three ways to lose fat. One,
walk more.
Two..." And you're like, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Instead of trying to take three good
points and putting them into one video,
just
take one of those points
and make it a standalone video.
Then, for instance,
you could say a video going,
"The hack bodybuilders don't want
you to know about.
Did you know there's a hack
that bodybuilders are using, and
they actually tell people,
but people don't believe them?
But if people just implemented this,
they could get much better results.
And I'm going to show you some studies
that back that up." And if you hadn't
guessed, that thing is walking. Now,
let's look at some other benefits apart
from
fat loss that walking could be good for.
That's a banger 90-second Reel. Okay.
Calorie calculator. Yeah.
So you're probably going to get some from
that. But yeah.
Inquiry for coaching. Inquiry.
Sorry to say this to you or anyone with a
lead form, I very much doubt you're
that important to require
inquiring. This is good. Don't stop this.
When it comes to videos, I always try to,
if I can, not put any text on it.
And I think there's such a good
opportunity,
if there's no text on the thumbnail,
to make people go to the title to find out
more information. So I'd try that.
And if you do put text on the thumbnail,
don't have it over you.
Emilia, I like the socials.
I feel like that your funnel
is super wide at the
top and then getting narrower quite fast.
Honestly, first of all,
if you're going to tell people to DM you,
have some
automation in place. Second thing,
don't give up on YouTube.
Third, the Linktree,
just don't get inquiry.
That could be more information about what
I do.
And in your sales video, you could say,
"And if you're not ready to buy now, why
not use the calculator down below
and work out your total daily energy
expenditure?" So then with the traffic
you're sending to your landing page,
you're
still collecting data.
You could also then have an abandoned
cart.
So if they do go through to finding out
how much it costs, you could actually get
their email address that way.
I'm going to give you a 6 out of 10,
because you've
been very consistent with the posts.
Your YouTube,
you're putting some good effort into.
You've already probably done the hardest
part, which is getting to 10,000
followers. If you
were to just have a nicer sales process
and not to do the damn
sales call.
Still nothing back from the DM.
Your wife's in my DMs. Okay,
the next one is a little bit different.
Okay, Alex. So we have Scale Swimming.
Okay. Clean.
Okay. One thing I'd be interested here,
if you're a team of swimming
instructors. "Our advice for swimmers
and triathletes." If you're a team,
this logo
is fine. But if you're one person,
I would love for you to be that
there.
But let's have a look at the content.
[upbeat music]
You know what time it is. Okay.
I would just love someone to own this page
and just
be front of house for it.
It's getting in my face.
Imagine coming up out the water.
"If swimming is your weak point in a
triathlon." Great hook.
I'm making these up.
"Wouldn't it be nice
if you could swim faster?
Are you someone that's embarrassed to go
to the pool at busy time because there are
people 25 years older than you
that can swim faster than you
and for longer?"
That's one of my insecurities. There
are so many hooks in swimming.
Get rid of this music.
Just talk to people.
Even a nice voiceover.
It's a bit chaotic, all of this.
Just because you like this type of music,
don't assume someone's just chilling at
home on the sofa, "Oh, swimming.
Yeah,
I wish I was better at that." [singing]
He's like,
"Fucking hell, mate." Okay.
I'm not mad on the content.
I'm not going to lie to you.
Motivation and advice for swimmers
and triathletes.
Let's maybe delete this bit where it says
Scale Swimming.
Let's just have motivation advice.
Waterproof training books
and more aids to help you swim faster.
Collabs.
Johnny.
I don't know what any of this means
if I'm honest.
For collabs, get rid of this.
Just let's have somewhere they can go.
Our shop and socials. Let's try this.
Let's try this. Okay.
Waterproof training book.
Buy our waterproof books.
I'm not sure what this is,
if I'm honest with you, mate.
10 resistance workouts
that incorporate equipment so you can
find...
But why do I need that as a book?
I would love to know your sales on
this.
I'm not sure anyone particularly needs
that. Scale Swimming.
1,000 subscribers. Not terrible.
These thumbnails got to stop.
Absolutely. What in the hell
is going on here?
Whoever's designing these for you,
please do not stop.
Should you stick to only freestyle in
training? Muscular ki...
Okay,
so there's actually some not bad things
here.
Should you stick to only freestyle in
training?
I think we could even word these a bit
better. Get fast,
quick scheme in swimming.
#swimming.
No need to put hashtags in the title.
Okay,
let's have a look at another channel.
What if I just put in swimming?
Effortless Swimming here,
300,000 subscribers.
You see how this guy, right-
Hi, Breton here from Effortless Swimming.
In today's video,
I'm going to talk about why you might
still be exhausted after
100 meters
This is what I want you to have.
And this guy, 1.4 million views.
Even in your swimming business,
you need someone to be front and center.
Even though he's not in a swimming pool
and he's in the front room, he's here
because he wants to help you.
That's why we're on this channel.
And if we can go here, sort of popular.
Look at these thumbnails. Okay?
They are so clean and crisp,
because as a viewer, I
guarantee these people wouldn't have found
these videos by search.
So in essence,
everyone seems to think on YouTube
that we search for videos, which
we do, but the majority of people browse.
So for instance, what I mean by that is,
I discover videos not by hitting them in
the search bar, I find them by doing this,
and I'm going and I go, "Oh,
Matt Armstrong's got a new video,"
which of course I've watched.
And it's only by scrolling. This
is how people are finding videos, right?
So the thumbnails here,
the reason these do so well
is you could blink, boom, and I
know what the video's about.
It's about swimming. That is pretty niche.
If I'm not interested in swimming,
my eye does this, just looks away.
But if I'm someone that swims,
I'm going to see that and be drawn to it.
Why these thumbnails are genius. Now,
what I'm going to do is the hierarchy.
I'm going to look at the thumbnail,
and then I'm going to try
and find out what
it's about by looking at the title.
See how they haven't put the title in the
thumbnail, thumbnail in the title.
This guy doesn't even look like he's
swimming freestyle.
How to swim faster freestyle.
There's your first video to go away
and make.
Here's your second one.
How to stop your legs from sinking in
freestyle.
Do you know why?
Because I would like to flipping watch
that one.
These are only four minutes long.
Oh, I'm on my wrong YouTube account.
That's embarrassing. Please forgive me.
Where is that channel?
We're just going to have to sit through
the advert because
I'm on the wrong fucking browser.
Or actually, let's go.
Effortless Swimming.
Hi,
Brenton Ford here from Effortless
Swimming.
I'll go over to me other browser, mate.
And I was just showing off Spanion.
Any of you that don't follow Spanion,
that's huge, brother.
We're talking about the DJI Pocket Osmo 3.
People were saying,
"Is it better than iPhone?" And I said,
"Depends what iPhone
you have." But Spanion here,
five million views using a DJI, brother.
That's huge.
So you can literally dominate YouTube
using that, but don't
get distracted.
Hi,
Brenton Ford here from Effortless
Swimming.
And today-
What did I tell you? A voiceover, bro.
There's no music,
there's no need for [singing]
Today,
you're going to learn why your legs sink
in freestyle-
Straight away in the beginning,
just telling me what it is I came for.
Why do my legs sink in freestyle?
... and how you can fix it so
that you're creating less drag,
and as a result of
that, swimming not only easier,
but faster as well.
That's the exact things
that I said earlier on in the hook.
People want to swim easier and faster.
That's it. That's what they want.
So straight away, this guy, in 13 seconds,
established the
problem and how to solve it,
and what the result will be as a
byproduct.
Fantastic. I guarantee this geezer
is getting leads coming in on the reg for
business or for products.
Let's have a look at what he's selling.
I don't think he's selling a waterproof
book.
Hi, Brenton here from Effortless Swimming.
All right, mate. Relax.
Effortless Swimming,
what a good brand name.
Now, yours was called, what?
Scale Swimming? Was it Scale Swimming?
Let's have a little look-see. See, look,
Scale Swimming is effortless swimming.
I think his branding's a bit better.
Look at this,
grab the eight-week Faster Freestyle
course.
This is where I think you're going to want
a little course or something.
I want to start swimming faster.
What a landing page.
Swim faster in eight weeks
or your money back.
I mean,
how can you not consider doing that?
This guy's banging videos on the tube
and just watching money.
Ching, ching, ching, ching.
What a fucking legend, mate.
Let's have a look at his Insta. Sorry,
we are getting distracted, aren't we?
Oh, I'm on the wrong browser. Don't worry.
Basically, look, I've got ADHD.
I use Chrome for some stuff.
I use Safari for others.
312 followers. Look at this. Clean, bro.
Look at the 5 point. Right, 5.8 million.
Let's imagine,
is this going to have music or...?
[upbeat music] Fuck.
He's done me dirty there.
That one does have music.
Maybe we actually had propulsion coming
from the kick.
In fact,
most of it should come from what the arms
are doing and your rotation.
All right,
so the other ones did have music,
but I guarantee this type of content
for his business is going to get him much
more business than just
having [upbeat music]
Guarantee it. Where were we? Cool. So,
waterproof training book.
I don't think anyone's ever woken up
and gone, "Babe,
I think we need a waterproof
training book." I think a swimming course
would be the go for you, if I'm honest.
I still think whoever the main person of
your business should be here, not this.
Looks like the back of Sonic's head.
What was Sonic's mate with the red hair
called? Knuckles.
Oh, God. That's mad, isn't it? All right.
So yeah, for some reason,
your brand there made me think of old
Knuckles'
hair. Where were we? I don't know.
Let's get back to it. Cool.
Scale Swimming. Three, I'm afraid.
And it's time for the last. Again,
I swear to God, I haven't looked
at any of these. Physio Co-op.
This won't take too long, will it?
Because you've done four posts, mate.
Four bloody posts.
I've done more than
that in the last fucking 24 hours, cat.
All right, look at that.
You're getting four times your following
on your reels.
What's this? Bloody dodgy Wi-Fi, is it?
Oh, God. What is going on here, mate?
I feel like-
Bridging the great exercise
if someone's suffering from lower back
pain and want
advice like-
Fantastically well spoken, sir. Now,
do you know what?
This type of content here isn't the best,
but it's good, because do you know what?
He's on the move,
he's got five minutes spare,
he's making content.
People use their low back during-
I like that to react to another piece of
content, he's full screened it
... exercise,
which takes away the work from their
glutes-
And he prefaced it.
He said something before it
... causing a lot of low back pain.
It's exactly what you need to be careful
as to
who you listen to on social media. Now,
if someone unsure how to activate-
Oh, look at that for a transition,
you dirty dog.
Mate, keep this up, you'll be flying.
Probably let's get a better picture of
your face, though. You know what I mean?
This is probably a little bit too close.
You know when people are like, "Hi, mate,
you all right?" If someone was to ever
stand 20% too close to your face,
you're like,
"Get the fuck out of my face."
20% too far away, you're like,
"Great." Can't smell what you had for
breakfast.
Mate, tell you what,
as far as a flipping bio, 10 out of 10 for
that. Quite simply, I help people in pain.
Fuck me, cunt.
What a fucking great bio.
I debunk a lot of bullshit
when it comes to treating
pain. Boom.
It's got a little Bitly going on.
You might be in my mentorship.
Now, one thing I will say
is this isn't a landing page, this
is a squeeze page,
okay?
A lot of people struggling with chronic
pain-
Although I implore the exceptional video,
and this is hosted on
Leadpages, tip my hat,
we don't need this much for a
squeeze for any of my marketing thing.
So we just need to think of something of
value that you could give someone, which
is what we have here,
"20 ways in 20 days to reduce pain." Let's
change this.
Pain free in under 3 weeks. Or you say,
"Give me three weeks and I'll reduce your
pain." I suppose it's difficult because
you can't promise that. Here you go.
This is what you need.
Let me give you three weeks of
evidence-based strategies to
help with pain. All I need
is your best email address.
Now, will say one thing,
not too sure about the layout here,
mate.
One trend that I'm seeing at the moment,
which I'm absolutely frothing, is
what I'd call dark mode.
These light backgrounds, the small texts,
I'd rather this
was dark with light text. Because then,
as a boy, you can get away with having
pretty mediocre color palettes.
Because let's be honest, women
are amazing at
design.
My missus just changed the bedsheets last
night.
We got this British racing green with this
tartan. It's amazing.
You can't leave a man to decide what
bedsheets you wear.
Dudes, when making landing pages,
go dark backdrop, light text.
Keep it easy.
Keep it simple. Now,
your title here says Understanding Pain.
This says 20 Ways in 20 Days to Reduce
Pain, but your best bit here is that.
Give me 20 days so I can... Or just say,
"Let me give you some
evidence-based strategies to help you
reduce it." Now, my only concern is,
Clarky
boy, I know you're a physio,
but not everyone is in pain.
I'm just trying to think. For a physio,
your in-person business is always good,
but
when it comes to online strategies,
I'm not quite sure what
is the golden elixir of
making money online.
But it's going to be us. Don't know.
Keep doing what you're doing.
And this needs probably a bit less
saturation, if I'm
honest. Road to 100 posts.
Like I said before,
if you'd like me to constructively
go through your social media,
there's a link in the description.
Make sure you buy Nutonic.
For every one of you
that doesn't purchase Nutonic,
somewhere in the world, a kitten dies.
And as per usual, YouTube,
with its smart algorithm, recommends
that you should
watch this video here.
I don't know what the video is.
YouTube recommended it.
And if you enjoyed this one,
you'll definitely love that one.
And this one will probably be a lot
shorter, because this one went on a bit,
didn't
it? All the best. Bye.